[OP, skip to 1:04]
[OP,跳到1:04]
Composer: Mickey
作曲 米奇
Planning: Mickey
企劃 米奇
Vocals: Mickey
演唱 米奇
Production: Mickey
製作 米奇
Editing: Mickey
剪輯 米奇
Cinematography: Mickey
攝影 米奇
Direction: Mickey
策划 米奇
Vocal Direction: Mickey
配唱 米奇
Tuning: Mickey
定音 米奇
Recording: Mickey
錄音 米奇
Inspiration: Mickey
靈感 米奇
Artist: Mickey
藝人 米奇
Screen: Mickey
螢幕 米奇
Music: Mickey
音樂 米奇
Inspiration: Mickey
靈感 米奇
Ringtone: Mickey
鈴聲 米奇
Music: Mickey
音樂 米奇
Inspiration: Mickey
靈感 米奇
Recording: Mickey
錄音 米奇
Outsiders: Mickey
外人 米奇
Music: Mickey
音樂 米奇
Truth and lies confuse our eyes
真真假假迷惑我们的眼
Use your heart to see it right
用你的心认真去看
The truth is never far from sight
发现真相就在不远
Hey you good or bad, truth or lies
Hey you good or bad 真真假假
Can't escape this soul's gray skies
逃不出这心灵的灰烟
Take all your courage, stand up tall
带上你的所有勇敢
Maybe you can save it all
也许就能拯救这世界
Mojo Mojo Mojo Spy
Mojo Mojo Mojo Spy
For your SPY
For your SPY
Voice of Beauty
美丽之声
【Tuna Town Selection Contest】
【金枪鱼选拔赛】
The final winner of this star selection contest is...
本次明星选拔大赛最终的获胜者是
The winner is...
获胜者是
Who is it?
是谁呢
Who is it? Who is it?
是谁呢 是谁呢
It's Miss MU!
是小MU!
Congratulations, Miss MU!
恭喜小MU!
Congrats!
恭喜
Oh, Miss MU, we love you!
哦 小MU我们爱你！
Thank you, thank you, everyone!
谢谢 谢谢大家
Ah, it's Miss MU!
啊 是小MU!
Miss MU, I love you!
小MU 我爱你
You see, our lovely citizens have everything—except an idol to worship.
你看,我们可爱的市民,他们什么都有,却唯独缺少用来崇拜的偶像
And you, you are the idol I created.
而你,就是我创造出来的偶像
What's wrong, big star? Mad? Haha.
怎么了,大明星生气了 哈哈
My favorite!
我的最爱
Good Juice Brand Juice.
好果汁牌果汁
Locky Qi!
齐乐天
Did you see that?
你看到了吗
See what?
看到什么
Miss MU likes the same juice as me!
小MU也和我一样喜欢喝果汁耶
Miss Jingjing.
菁菁小姐
Please stay calm.
请你保持冷静
What's so great about a TV star?
一个电视明星有什么了不起的
If you like me,
喜欢我
come to my concert!
就来看我的演唱会
【Miss MU Tuna Town Concert】
【小MU金枪鱼演唱会】
【Coming Soon!】
【震撼推出】
So cool! Yeah!
好酷！耶!
Kids!
孩子们
Move it, move it, move it!
让开 让开 让开
Hey, my kid has no manners.
诶 我家的孩子真没礼貌
Looks like these two tickets to Miss MU's concert in my hand
看来我手里这两张小MU演唱会的门票
can only go to other, more well-behaved kids.
只能送给别人家更懂礼貌的孩子了
Concert!!
演唱会！！
Old man! I love you to death!
老舅！我爱死你了
Hey, stop, stop! I'll give you the tickets, stop!
诶 停下 停下 票我给你们 停下！
Yahoo!
呀吼
Yes.
是的
I'm standing right at the entrance of the Tuna Stadium concert venue for the superstar Miss MU.
我正站在天后小MU金枪鱼体育馆演唱会的现场的入口
Tens of thousands of fans, dressed in festive attire,
数以万计的歌迷身着节日盛装
have come here to watch Miss MU's concert.
来到这里观看小MU的演唱会
In just one hour, just one hour,
再过一个小时就一个小时
we'll enter the venue
我们将进入会场
and bring you an explosive live broadcast.
为您带来劲爆十足的实况转播
After the commercial break,
广告之后
we'll be right back.
马上回来
This packet of medicine is for you.
这包药给你
Just mix it in water and have her take it,
只要混在水中让她服下
and your wish will come true.
就可以达成你的心愿了
You... why are you helping me?
你 你为什么要帮我
Everything I do is about performing beauty,
我所做的一切都是在演绎美丽
about interpreting art.
在诠释艺术
You don't need to ask me why.
你并不需要问我原因
Once my work is complete,
待到我的作品全部完成
the whole world will be captivated by it.
整个世界都将 被它折服
As for you,
至于你
don't ask so many questions.
也不用问那么多
Just do as I say.
照我说的做就行
W-Will this kill him?
这 这会不会要了他的命
Don't worry.
放心
Her conscience is drowning in guilt right now.
她的良心正承受巨大的愧疚
This packet of powder will be her salvation.
这包药粉完全可以拯救她
Soon enough,
用不了多久
she'll become the most beautiful sleeping beauty in the world.
她就会变成世界上最漂亮的睡美人
[Dressing Room]
[化妆间]
Wen Kang, you're here.
文康 你来了
Xiao Miao, the concert's about to start.
小妙 演唱会马上开始了
Have some juice to wet your throat first.
先喝杯果汁润润嗓子吧
Thanks, Wen Kang.
谢谢文康
But I'm in the middle of putting on lipstick.
可我正在抹口红
Be good.
乖
Drink the juice first, then we'll talk.
你先把果汁喝了再说
You're so bossy.
你好霸道
Fine.
好啦
There, all done.
喝完了
Hmm? Oh, you.
嗯？ 你呀
You've been a dancer for so long,
当舞者都这么久了
and you're still this nervous before a show.
居然演出前还这么紧张
Shaking like a leaf.
居然紧张得发抖
Oh, right.
对了
I should go change too.
我也该去换衣服了
Heh heh, my big star, the show's about to start.
呵呵 我的大明星 演出马上就要开始了
Are you ready?
你准备好了吗
Oh wow, Miss MU
喔 哇 小MU
Oh wow, Miss MU, oh wow, Miss MU
喔哇 小MU 喔哇 小MU
Get ready
准备好
Miss MU, Miss MU, I love you
小MU小MU 我爱你
Miss MU, I love you
小MU我爱你
Stopped?
停止了？
[ED]
【ED】
Look at tomorrow, waving to me from your screen
看看明天 在你屏线向我招手
Every day in sunrise and sunset, turning time into more dreams
每天就在日升日落 转进时间幻想更多
Expecting every second, every moment of life
期待生命中 每秒每一刻
Bright eyes are sparkling, smiles facing the sunlight
明亮的眼睛在闪烁 迎着阳光的笑容
Treading softly at the crossroads of battle
踏步悄悄中在战家的路口